Guide to the Fedor Stepun Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1943-65; Series I; 16; (41 boxes)
  - GENERAL FILES
    - "H" General, 1946-64, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 442-449)
      - _ Izdatel'stvo imeni Chekhova, 1953-56 (Box 15, Folder 518)
        - Jakob Hegner Verlag in Köln, 1953-65 (Box 15, Folder 522)
        - Janentzky, C., 1954-57 (Box 15, Folder 523)
        - Jansen, Georg, 1963-64 (Box 15, Folder 524)
        - J.G. Cotta'sche Buchhandlung, 1958-60 (Box 15, Folder 525)
        - Joachim Jungius-Gesellschaft der Wissenschaften (Hamburg), 1952 (Box 15, Folder 526)
        - Johann Wolfgang Goethe-Universität Frankfurt-am-Main, 1954-56 (Box 15, Folder 527)
          Includes correspondence from: Der Dekan der Wirtschafts- und Sozialwissenschaftlichen Fakultät (K. Hax), Philosophische Fakultät
        - Johannes Guttenberg-Universität in Mainz, 1950-61 (Box 15, Folder 528)
      - _ John, Archbishop, 1945-64, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 529)
        Also known as: Ioann Shakhovskoi
        - Joseph Habbel Buch- und Kunstverlag, 1947-62 (Box 15, Folder 530)
        - Jucker, Ernst, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 531)
        - Jugend Europas (Box 15, Folder 532)
      - _ Jung, Georg, 1947-64 (Box 15, Folder 533)
        - "K" General, 1947-65, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 534-543)
      - _ Kaden, Lalla, 1946-61 (Box 16, Folder 544)
        - Kaempfe, Alexander, 1958-63 (Box 16, Folder 545)
      - _ Kaesebier, Grete, 1947-64 (Box 16, Folder 546)
        - Kall, Marie Luise, 1955-56 (Box 16, Folder 547)
      - _ Kállay, Adelheid von, 1952-60, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 548)
      - _ Kaminski, Clemens, 1948-55 (Box 16, Folder 549)
        - Kant-Gesellschaft, 1948-49 (Box 16, Folder 550)
      - _ Karmann, Rudolf, 1949-64 (Box 16, Folder 551)
      - _ Karpovich, Michael, 1948-58, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 552)
        Also spelled: Mikhail M. Karpovich Includes correspondence by Russian Review, Novyi Zhurnal
      - Kartasheva, P., 1958-64, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 553)
        See also: Russkaia Akademicheskaia Gruppa
      - _ Katholische Akademie in Bayern, 1959-64 (Box 16, Folder 554)
        - Katholische Bayerische Studenten- Verbindung Rhaetia, 1960-61 (Box 16, Folder 555)
        - Katolische deutsche Studenten- Einigung, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 556)
        - Katholische Hochschulgemeinde München, 1948-60 (Box 16, Folder 557)
        - Katholische Kulturgemeinde (Erlangen), 1947 (Box 16, Folder 558)
        - Katholische Studentengemeinde (Aachen), 1961-63 (Box 16, Folder 559)
        - Katholische Studentengemeinde (Frankfurt), 1956-62 (Box 16, Folder 560)
      - _ Katholische Studentengemeinde (Box 16, Folder 561)
        - (Freiburg), 1952-57
        - Katholische Studentengemeinde (Heidelberg), 1955 (Box 16, Folder 562)
        - Katholische Süddeutsche Studentenverbindung Alemannia, 1957-62 (Box 16, Folder 563)
        - Katholischer Akademikerverband (Berlin and Lörrach), 1952-59 (Box 16, Folder 564)
        - Katholischer Hochschulering Münster, 1947-60 (Box 16, Folder 565)
        - Katholisches Bildungswerk (Heidelberg), 1948 (Box 16, Folder 566)
        - Kennedy, ?, 1950 Apr 1 (Box 16, Folder 567)
        - Kepingov, Leonid, 1956-61 (Box 16, Folder 568)
      - _ Kerensky, Alexander, 1952-64, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 569)
        - Keyserling, Hermann, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 570)
      - _ Keyserling Gesellschaft für freie (Box 17, Folder 571)
        - Philosophie (Hamburg), 1953-56
          Includes: H. Pascual Jordan
      - _ Keyserling Gesellschaft für freie (Box 17, Folder 572)
        - Philosophie (Wiesbaden), 1950-61, n.d.
          Includes: E. Dungern
        - K.F. Koehler Verlag, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 573)
        - Khomiakov, Gennadii, 1959-65 (Box 17, Folder 574)
          Pseudonym: G. Andreev
        - Kilius, Albert, 1952-53 (Box 17, Folder 575)
        - Kindermann, Karl, 1947-51 (Box 17, Folder 576)
      - _ Kindler Verlag, 1956-63 (Box 17, Folder 577)
        - Kirchlicher Kunstdienst, 1952-57 (Box 17, Folder 578)
      - _ Kirchner-Kruse, Annemarie, 1953-58 (Box 17, Folder 579-580)
        - Kirschbaum, Emil, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 581)
          Includes: Institut für Apparatebau
      - _ Kiselev, A. (Box 17, Folder 582)
        - Kiseleva, M., 1948-61, n.d.
        - Klager, F., 1947-48 (Box 17, Folder 583)
        - Klasen, Anton, 1954-64 (Box 17, Folder 584)
          Includes: Klasen und Klasen
        - Klauser, Käthe, 1950-52 (Box 17, Folder 585)
        - Klein, Woldemar, 1951-62 (Box 17, Folder 586)
          Includes: Woldemar Klein Verlag
        - Kleist, Helmut Nikolai, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 587)
        - Klenovskii, Dmitrii, 1956-64 (Box 17, Folder 588)
        - Klingner, Hedwig Klingner, Friedrich, 1954-64 (Box 17, Folder 589)
      - _ Klippgen, Herbert (Box 17, Folder 590)
        - Klippgen, Gisela, 1945-64
        - Klippgen, Jost, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 591)
      - _ Klum, Edith (nee Bohmer), 1954-64, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 592-593)
        - Knoblauch, Johanna, 1947-50 (Box 17, Folder 594)
        - Knüpffer, Arthur, 1948-59 (Box 17, Folder 595)
        - Knüpffer, Rudolf von, 1953-64 (Box 17, Folder 596)
        - Koch, Gerda, 1954-63 (Box 17, Folder 597)
        - Koch, Marie, 1951-54 (Box 17, Folder 598)
        - Koch, Nikolaus, 1950-51 (Box 17, Folder 599)
        - Kodrianskaia, Natalia, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 600)
        - Kölner Zeitschrift für Soziologie, 1950-61 (Box 17, Folder 601)
      - _ König, Heinrich, 1947-64 (Box 17, Folder 602)
        - Konovalov, Evgenii, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 603)
      - _ Kosnick, Heinrich, 1958-61 (Box 17, Folder 604)
      - _ Kösel Verlag, 1946-64, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 605-607)
        Includes: O. Hoentzsch
      - Kotomkin, Aleksandr, 1954-58 (Box 17, Folder 608)
      - Kovalevskii, Petr Evgrafovich, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 609)
        Also known as: Pierre Kovalevsky
      - Kozhevnikov, V. Kozhevnikova, S., 1948-54, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 610)
      - _ Kozik, Alfred, 1953-64 (Box 17, Folder 611)
        - Krass, Paul, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 612)
        - Kraus, Erwin, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 613)
        - Krause, Erich, 1959-61 (Box 18, Folder 614)
        - Krefelder Museums-Verein, 1947-48 (Box 18, Folder 615)
        - Kreissl, Kurt, 1950-56 (Box 18, Folder 616)
        - Krieger, Arnold, 1959-61 (Box 18, Folder 617)
        - Kromiadi, K., 1957, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 618)
      - _ Kroner, Richard (Box 18, Folder 619-621)
        - Kroner, Alice, 1946-64, n.d.
          See also: box 70 folder 2200
        - Krüger, Gerhard, 1951 Jul 11 (Box 18, Folder 622)
        - Krüger, Valeska, 1961-64 (Box 18, Folder 623)
        - Krylova, V., 1958-61 (Box 18, Folder 624)
          Includes: Russkaia biblioteka
        - Ksenofontov, Vlas, 1949-50 (Box 18, Folder 625)
          Also spelled: Wlass Ksenofontow
        - Kuenelt-Leddihn, Erick, 1953-54 (Box 18, Folder 626)
      - _ Kühn, Johannes (Box 18, Folder 627-629)
        - Kühn, Lucia, 1944-65
        - Kuhn, Martin, 1947-48 (Box 18, Folder 630)
        - Kühn-Frobenius, Lenore, 1951-54, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 631)
          Includes typescript by L. Kühn- Frobenius
        - Kühner-Wolfskehl, Hans, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 632)
        - Kullmann, Gustav G., 1956 Jun 27 (Box 18, Folder 633)
          Also known as Gustav Kul'man
      - _ Kullmann, Maria (nee Zernova), 1945-64, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 634-636)
        Also known as Mariia Kul'man
      - Die Kultur, 1959-60 (Box 18, Folder 637)
      - Kulturgemeinde Siegen, 1947-57 (Box 18, Folder 638)
      - Kulturkreis beim Flüchtlingskommisar, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 639)
      - Kulturreferat der Stadt Pappenheim, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 640)
      - Kulturverein Gevelsberg, 1953-56 (Box 18, Folder 641)
      - Kulturverein Redenfelden-Raubling, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 642)
      - Kuntze, A. Helmut, 1947-51 (Box 18, Folder 643)
      - Kuprianoff, J., 1946-57 (Box 18, Folder 644)
        Includes correspondence from Reichsforschungsansalt für Lebensmittelnfrischhaltung
      - Kuprianoff, Maria, 1953, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 645)
      - Kurganov, I. A., 1955-59, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 646)
      - Kuskova, Ekaterina, 1949 Dec 14 (Box 18, Folder 647)
      - Küster, Matthias, 1950-51 (Box 18, Folder 648)
      - Kuzillo, Valentina, 1953-61 (Box 18, Folder 649)
      - Kuznetsova, Galina, 1959-62 (Box 18, Folder 650)
      - Kuzovlov, Aleksei, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 651)
        Also spelled: Alexej Kusowlow
      - "L" General, 1944-64, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 652-658)
      - Lagemann, Ulrich, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 659)
      - _ Lahme, Walter (Box 19, Folder 660)
        - Lahme, Katherina, 1961-62, n.d.
        - Lamprecht, Elisabeth, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 661)
        - Landesbühne Hannover, 1956-64 (Box 19, Folder 662)
          Includes: R. Rüdiger
        - Landesversicherunganstalt Oberbayen, 1952-53 (Box 19, Folder 663)
        - Lange, Bernard, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 664)
      - _ Lange, N. (Box 19, Folder 665-669)
        - Lange, Hermann, 1944-65, n.d.
        - Lapchinskii, Dmitrii, 1950-51 (Box 19, Folder 670)
        - Larese, Dino, 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 671)
          Includes correspondence from Schweizerischer Vortragsverband
      - _ Larka, Blanche, 1958-63, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 672)
        - La Roche, Maria, 1950-51 (Box 19, Folder 673)
        - Lauge, Woldemar, 1951-52 (Box 19, Folder 674)
      - _ Lauth, Reinhard, 1949-60 (Box 19, Folder 675)
        - Lebedev, Fedor Tarasovich, 1964-65 (Box 19, Folder 676)
        - Lechfeld Technische Schule, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 677)
        - Lednicki, Waclaw, 1959 May 3 (Box 19, Folder 678)
        - Leep, Hans Jürgen, 1963-64 (Box 19, Folder 679)
          See also: Der Bund Wuppertal
        - Leibniz-Kolleg der Universität Tübingen, 1955-57 (Box 19, Folder 680)
      - _ Lenel, Hans Otto (Box 19, Folder 681)
        - Lenel, Dorothea Lenel, Annemaria, 1947-64
      - _ Leontovitsch, Victor, 1944-59 (Box 20, Folder 682)
        Also spelled: Viktor Leontovich
      - Leuchtenbergskii, D. de, 1945-65 (Box 20, Folder 683)
      - Levin, Arthur, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 684)
      - Levitskii, S., 1946-59 (Box 20, Folder 685)
      - _ Lietz, Gertrude (Box 20, Folder 686)
        - Lietz, Alphons C., 1946-64, n.d.
        - Lietz, Heinrich, 1947-48 (Box 20, Folder 687)
      - _ Lilienfeld, Fairy von, 1948-57 (Box 20, Folder 688)
      - _ Lindert, Gertrude, 1950-51 (Box 20, Folder 689)
        - Linhart, Paula, 1946-55, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 690)
        - Linnebach, Irene, 1944, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 691)
        - Linz, Eugen, 1952-53 (Box 20, Folder 692)
          Includes correspondence from Elisabeth Weddingen
        - Lippstadt (City), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 693)
      - _ List, V., 1951-62 (Box 20, Folder 694)
        - Literarische Gesellschaft Gräfelfing, 1948-64 (Box 20, Folder 695)
        - Literarische Gesellschaft Wuppertal, 1946-48 (Box 20, Folder 696)
        - Literarische Vereinigung Bielefeld, 1948-50 (Box 20, Folder 697)
        - Literarische Verienigung Winterthur, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 698)
        - Literaturnyi Sovremennik, 1954-55 (Box 20, Folder 699)
          Includes: B. IAkolvlev
        - Litt, Theodor, 1945-61 (Box 20, Folder 700)
      - _ Liubimtsev, M., 1947-61 (Box 20, Folder 701)
        - Liubomirov, Nikolai, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 702)
        - Loesch, Ronald, 1947-63 (Box 20, Folder 703)
      - _ Löffler, Walter, 1957-64 (Box 20, Folder 704-705)
        Includes photographs of Löffler, Evgeniia Rap
      - Lohmer, Bert Lohmer, Ruth, 1948-63, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 706)
      - _ Lohmer, Eveline, 1951-64, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 707)
        - Lohr, Renata, 1959-63 (Box 20, Folder 708)
          Includes: Haus Venio
        - Lortz, Joseph, 1952-64, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 709)
          Includes: Institut für europäische Geschichte
        - Losskii, Boris Nikolaevich, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 710)
        - Losskii, Nikolai Onufrievich, 1950-59 (Box 20, Folder 711)
      - _ Luchtenberg, Paul (Box 20, Folder 712)
        - Luchtenberg, Else, 1947-64, n.d.
        - Luebke, Heinrich, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 713)
          President of W. Germany
        - Lugowoi, Nikolai, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 714)
      - _ Luther, Arthur, 1944-53 (Box 20, Folder 715)
        - Luzerner Neueste Nachrichten, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 716)
        - "M" General, 1946-64, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 717-722)
      - _ McFalls, Richard, 1956-61 (Box 21, Folder 723)
      - _ Mackiewicz, Josef, 1957-64 (Box 21, Folder 724)
        Includes correspondence from P. E. N.
      - Mager, Ingeborg, 1958-62 (Box 21, Folder 725)
      - Magyarorszag szabadsaga-vilagbeke (Hungary's Freedom Worldpeace), 1962-4 (Box 21, Folder 726)
      - Makarov, A., 1946-64 (Box 21, Folder 727)
      - _ Malakhova, M., 1957-63, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 728)
      - _ Maler, E., 1949-64 (Box 21, Folder 729)
        - Manesse Verlag, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 730)
          Includes: W. Meier, Frida Gadamer
      - _ Mangoldt, Carmila, 1956-62, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 731)
        - Mann, Thomas, 1931 Feb 18 (Box 21, Folder 732)
          Photostat
        - Mannheim (City), 1952-53 (Box 21, Folder 733)
      - _ Manns, Peter, 1956-63 (Box 21, Folder 734)
        Includes correspondence from Institut für europäische Geschichte
      - Mantzke, Martin, 1963-64 (Box 21, Folder 735)
      - Marcinkowski, Heinz, 1946-49 (Box 21, Folder 736)
      - Marck, Claire, 1959-62 (Box 21, Folder 737)
      - Maria L. Bohnenberger Europa-Verlag, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 738)
        Includes typescript "Hoffnung ist eine gute Tat"
      - Markov, V., 1962-64 (Box 21, Folder 739)
      - Marshall, Mathilde, 1957-60 (Box 21, Folder 740)
      - _ Martin, Alfred von, 1944-62 (Box 21, Folder 741)
        - Maslenikov, Oleg R., 1957 Jan 25 (Box 21, Folder 742)
          Includes offprint
        - Matern, Anneliese and Aloys, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 743)
        - Matthaes, Ruth, 1960-64 (Box 21, Folder 744)
      - _ Mathieu, Maria, 1949-52 (Box 21, Folder 745)
        - Matveeva, Irina, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 746)
        - Mauk, Marielies, 1946-62 (Box 21, Folder 747)
        - Maurer, Johannes, 1961-63 (Box 21, Folder 748)
      - _ Maurina, Zenta, 1959-64 (Box 21, Folder 749)
        - Maus, Leopold, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 750)
      - _ Maximillian Dietrich Verlag, 1951-64 (Box 21, Folder 751)
        - May, Elizabeth (Bettina) May, John Rayner, 1951-52 (Box 21, Folder 752)
        - Mayer, Oskar, 1947-54 (Box 21, Folder 753)
        - Mayer-Gunthof, Franz, 1959-61 (Box 21, Folder 754)
      - _ Mecklenburg, Georg zu, 1947-63 (Box 22, Folder 755)
        - Medem, Fedor Aleksandrovich, Graf, 1958-64 (Box 22, Folder 756)
        - Mederow, Paul Wolfgang, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 757)
      - _ Medtner, Nikolai Karlovich (Box 22, Folder 758)
        - Medtner, Anna, 1948-59
          Also spelled: Metner
        - Mehnert, Klaus, 1949-60 (Box 22, Folder 759)
          See also: Deutsche Gesellschaft für Osteuropakunde
        - Meier, Bernhard, 1953-56 (Box 22, Folder 760)
        - Meier, Herbert, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 761)
      - _ Mel'gunov, P. (Box 22, Folder 762)
        - Mel'gunova, S., 1949-56, n.d.
          Also spelled: Melgounoff Includes: Vozrozhdenie
        - Menn, Wilhelm, 1946-47 (Box 22, Folder 763)
        - Mensch und Technik. Darmstädter Gespräch und Ausstellung 1952 (Box 22, Folder 764)
      - _ Menzel, Hans, 1947-57 (Box 22, Folder 765)
        - Merian, Hans-Rudolf, 1951-53 (Box 22, Folder 766)
      - _ Merkur, 1946-65 (Box 22, Folder 767)
        Includes: Hans Paeschke, J. Moras
        - Mertens, Josef, 1953-61 (Box 22, Folder 768)
        - Merz, Hilde, 1961-63 (Box 22, Folder 769)
        - Metzger, Arnold, 1959-62 (Box 22, Folder 770)
      - _ Meuschel, Stefan (Box 22, Folder 771)
        - Meuschel, Suzanne (nee Lüpertz), 1958-63
          See also: Studentischer Filmclub an der Universität Bonn
        - Meusel, Joachim, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 772)
        - Meyer, Hans Chanoch, 1960-61 (Box 22, Folder 773)
        - Mikhailovskii, A., 1947-64 (Box 22, Folder 774)
      - _ Mildner, Paul (Box 22, Folder 775-776)
        - Mildner, Irmengard, 1946-64
          Includes correspondence from Dietrich Gidionsen
        - Military Government for Bavaria, 1947, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 777)
        - Millioti, M., 1951-54 (Box 22, Folder 778)
        - Miltiz, Monica Grafin, 1945-64 (Box 22, Folder 779)
      - _ Minchenko, IAkov Arsenievich (Box 22, Folder 780-782)
        - Minchenko, Ekaterina, 1945-63, n.d.
      - _ Miroliubov, J. (Box 22, Folder 783)
        - Miroliubov, IU., 1961-62
        - Mohr, Eduard M.R., 1961-62 (Box 23, Folder 784)
        - Mohr, Elisabeth Mohr, Kurt, 1947-54 (Box 23, Folder 785)
        - Mohrenschildt, Dimitri Sergius von, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 786)
          See also: The Russian Review
        - Molineus, Kurt Molineus, Lise, 1952-62, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 787)
      - _ Die Monat, 1950-64 (Box 23, Folder 788)
        - Montgelas, Paul Graf, 1948-64 (Box 23, Folder 789)
      - _ Moor, B., 1940-61, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 790)
        - Moos, Xaver von, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 791)
      - _ Morozov, Ivan Vasil'evich, 1950-65 (Box 23, Folder 792)
        Also known as: Jean Morosov Includes correspondence from Action chrétienne des étudiants russes; Les éditeurs Réunis; YMCA-Press
        - Mosely, Philip E., 1951-53 (Box 23, Folder 793)
        - Mozharovskaia, L., 1946-61 (Box 23, Folder 794)
        - M. S. Metz Verlag, 1952-53 (Box 23, Folder 795)
        - Muffat, Karl-Heinz, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 796)
        - Mülheim an die Ruhr (City), 1952-54 (Box 23, Folder 797)
      - _ Müller, Aloys, 1956-60 (Box 23, Folder 798)
        - Müller, Eberhard, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 799)
      - _ Müller, Elisabetha, 1946-64 (Box 23, Folder 800)
        - Müller, Erika v., 1954-64 (Box 23, Folder 801)
        - Müller, Hans Maria, 1949-64 (Box 23, Folder 802)
          Includes correspondence from Brüder Auer Verlag
        - Müller, K. Valentin Müller, Lisolette (nee Knofel), 1946-63 (Box 23, Folder 803)
      - _ Müller, Ludolf, 1950-64 (Box 23, Folder 804)
        - Müller-Solomatin, Gerda, 1949-50 (Box 23, Folder 805)
        - Müller und Kiepenheuer Verlag, 1947-49 (Box 23, Folder 806)
          Includes correspondence from Weltliteratur
      - _ München (City), 1947-64 (Box 23, Folder 807)
        - München und Freising. Erzdiözese (M. Defregger, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 808)
        - Münchner Grosskomturei, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 809)
        - Münchner Kammerspiele, 1950-62 (Box 23, Folder 810)
        - Münchner Merkur, 1950-51 (Box 23, Folder 811)
        - Münchner Studentenzeitung, 1947-48 (Box 23, Folder 812)
        - Münchner Volkhochschule, 1946-52 (Box 23, Folder 813)
      - _ Murav'ev, P., 1945-62 (Box 23, Folder 814)
        - Museum "Die Fähre" Saulgau, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 815)
        - Musik-Verlag Wilhelm Zimmerman, 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 816)
      - _ Muth, Jakob Friedrich (Box 23, Folder 817)
        - Muth, Ottmar H. Muth, Wolfgang, 1948-63
        - "N" General, 1946-64 (Box 24, Folder 818-819)
        - Nabokov, S., 1951 (Box 24, Folder 820)
        - Nägel, Adolf, 1961-63 (Box 24, Folder 821)
      - _ Nägel, Andreas, 1948-61 (Box 24, Folder 822)
        - Nägel, Luise, 1946-53 (Box 24, Folder 823)
        - Nationaltheater Mannheim, 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 824)
        - Natsional'noe Predstavitel'stvo Rossiiskoi Emigratsii, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 825)
        - Neger, Marianne, 1952, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 826)
        - Neubau, 1946-47 (Box 24, Folder 827)
        - Neubauer, Helmut, 1952-57 (Box 24, Folder 828)
        - Die Neue Bund, 1960-61 (Box 24, Folder 829)
        - Die Neue Ordnung, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 830)
        - Die Neue Zeitung, 1947-52 (Box 24, Folder 831)
        - Neues Abendland, 1948-51 (Box 24, Folder 832)
      - _ Neumann, Carl (Box 24, Folder 833-835)
        - Neumann, Hedwig Neumann, Grete, 1945-64
        - Neumann, Elisabeth (nee Molineus), 1950-52 (Box 24, Folder 836)
        - Neumann, Fritz Neumann, Ruth, 1946-62 (Box 24, Folder 837)
        - Neumann, Peter, 1951-64 (Box 24, Folder 838)
          Includes: P. C. Neumann GMBH
        - Neumann, Heinzgeorg, 1947-50 (Box 24, Folder 839)
        - Nielsen, Thor, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 840)
        - Nigg, Walter, 1960-64 (Box 24, Folder 841)
        - Nicolaevsky, Boris, 1947-48 (Box 24, Folder 842)
        - Nil'skii, Mikhail, 1956-59 (Box 24, Folder 843)
      - _ Noetzel, Sofie, 1946-64 (Box 24, Folder 844)
        - Nolden, Margarete, 1948-50 (Box 24, Folder 845)
      - _ Norddeutscher Rundfunk, 1948-64 (Box 24, Folder 846-847)
        - Nordrhein-Westfalen, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 848)
        - Nordwestdeutscher Rundfunk, 1948-54 (Box 24, Folder 849)
        - Notizen. Tübinger Studentenzeitung, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 850)
        - Notverband amtsverdränglicher Hochschullehrer, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 851)
      - _ Novikov, Mikhail M., 1949-61 (Box 24, Folder 852)
        - Novikov, Viacheslav, 1960, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 853)
        - Novitskii, Evgenii I., 1948-61 (Box 24, Folder 854)
        - Novoye Russkoye Slovo, 1957-60 (Box 24, Folder 855)
      - _ Nymphenburger Verlagshandlung, 1947-54 (Box 24, Folder 856)
        Includes correspondence from B. Spangelberg, Deutsche Beitrage
      - _ Nyssen, Wilhelm, 1958-64 (Box 24, Folder 857)
        - "O" General, 1944-64 (Box 25, Folder 858-859)
        - Oberhausen (City), 1958 (Box 25, Folder 860)
        - Obolenskii, Dmitrii Nikolaevich, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 861)
        - Oestereich, Sigrid, 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 862)
        - Ofrosimov, IUrii Viktorovich, 1952, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 863)
      - _ Open Veld Ontmoetingen, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 864)
        - Opyty, 1953-56 (Box 25, Folder 865)
          See also: R. Grinberg
        - Ordo: Jahrbuch für die Ordnung von Wirtschaft und Gesellschaft, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 866)
        - Ortloff, Alexander, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 867)
        - Osherova, Polina IUl'evna, 1961-3 (Box 25, Folder 868)
          Includes cover letter from Irina Saburova
        - Osipov, N., 1946, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 869)
        - Osorgin, M., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 870)
        - Ostakademie Königstein, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 871)
      - _ Ostdeutsche Kulturrat, 1959-63 (Box 25, Folder 872)
        - Ostdeutsche Monatschefte, 1959-60 (Box 25, Folder 873)
        - Österreichisches College, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 874)
        - Osteuropa. Zeitschrift für gegenwartsfragen des Osten, 1951-63 (Box 25, Folder 875)
      - _ Osteuropa-Institut an der (Box 25, Folder 876)
        - Universität Freiburg, 1954-63
        - Ostpreussische Arztfamilie, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 877)
        - Otto Wilhelm Barth-Verlag, 1951-58 (Box 25, Folder 878)
        - "P" General, 1944-64, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 879-883)
        - Pädagogische Arbeitsstätte, 1950-51 (Box 26, Folder 884)
        - Pascal, Pierre, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 885)
        - Pascual Jordan, Hertha, 1953-61 (Box 26, Folder 886)
          See also: Keyserling Gesellschaft für freie philosophie (Hamburg)
        - Pasternak, Boris Leonidovich, 1960 May 6 (Box 26, Folder 887)
          Includes typescript copy
        - Paul List Verlag, 1958-63 (Box 26, Folder 888)
        - Paulus-Gesellschaft, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 889)
        - Pavlov, A., 1960-64 (Box 26, Folder 890)
        - Pedersen, Traute, 1959-60 (Box 26, Folder 891)
        - P. E. N. Internationale Schrift- stellervereinigung, 1949-59 (Box 26, Folder 892)
          Includes: Deutsches PEN-Zentrum der Bundesrespublik; Vorbereitender Ausschuss des Exil- Penzentrum; Pauls Kovalevskis-Klans; Latvija. Latvian Newspaper
          See also: J. Mackiewicz
      - _ La pensée russe, 1951-65 (Box 26, Folder 893)
        Includes: S. Vodov, W. Wesselowsky
        - Pescetto, Albert, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 894)
        - Pestalozzi-Gymnasium Herne, 1953-54 (Box 26, Folder 895)
        - Petersdorff, Gertrude von, 1948-54, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 896)